Here we have a constructor function called Hero,
这是一个叫做 Hero 的构造函数
which creates objects with a few properties,
它会创建具有几个属性的对象
when we invoke this function with a new keyword.
当我们使用关键字 new 调用该函数时
The name that we pass in will be the value of a new object's name property.
我们传入的名字将为新对象的 name 属性的值
Likewise, the role that we pass on will become the value of the role property,
同样 我们传入的角色将为 role 属性的值
the newly created object will also have a method called introduce,
新建的对象还将有一个叫做 introduce 的方法
which simply prints a message to the console using the objects,
该方法会使用对象的 name 和 role 属性
name, and role properties.
向控制台中输出一条消息
Let's go ahead and invoke Hero,
我们调用 Hero
and instantiate a few new objects.
并初始化几个新的对象
Here we called the Hero constructor function using the new keyword,
我们使用关键字 new 调用了 Hero 构造函数
and pass it to arguments,
传入几个参数
we pass in the string "Taylor" to represent the name,
传入字符串“Taylor” 表示名字
and we also pass in the string "mother" to represent the role.
并传入字符串“mother” 表示角色
Calling this function with a new instantiates a new object,
使用关键字 new 调用该函数初始化了新的对象
which is referenced by the "Taylor" variable over here.
由这里的变量“Taylor”来引用
Likewise we use the same constructor function and call it with new again,
同样 我们使用 new 调用相同的构造函数
and passed it a string of "Riley" and a string "coach" to create a new object.
并传入字符串“Riley”和“coach”新建一个对象
Let's go ahead and check out a few properties,
我们看看几个属性
and then have the objects introduce themselves.
然后让对象自我介绍一下
We can see that accessing by
通过“Taylor”对象的 name 属性
name property of the "Taylor" object returns
进行访问返回了“Taylor”
"Taylor" which is what we passed into the constructor function over here.
它是在这里传入构造函数中的字符串
Let's check out some of the "Riley" object's properties.
我们看看“Riley”对象的属性
Great.
好
We can see that accessing the role property of
访问“Riley”对象的 role 属性
the "Riley" object gives us a string "coach",
获得了字符串“coach”
which is exactly what we pass the constructor function over here.
正是我们在这里传入构造函数中的字符串
Let us go ahead and call the introduce method on each object.
我们针对每个对象调用 introduce 方法
Awesome. So keep in mind that since we called
注意 因为我们
introduce as a method onto the "Taylor" object,
在“Taylor”对象上调用了方法 introduce
the value of this gets set to the object itself,
this 的值设为了对象本身
meaning that we can grab Taylor from this tag name,
表示我们可以从 this.name 中获取 Taylor
and we can also grab "mother", from this.role.
并且可以从 this.role 获取 mother
Same goes for the "Riley" object when we call introduce on the "Riley" object.
“Riley”对象也一样 当我们对“Riley”对象调用 introduce 时
We grab Riley's name property which is a string "Riley" and
我们获取了 Riley 的 name 属性 即字符串“Riley”
we also grab Riley's role property which is "coach."
我们还获取了 Riley 的 role 属性 即“coach”
What's great about constructor functions,
构造函数的好处是
is that we can call the same constructor function and
我们可以调用相同的构造函数
create as many instances or objects as we like.
创建无数个实例或对象